netins.net 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy | netINS

IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC., Inc. has provided this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.iowanetworkservices.com.

## Information

IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC., Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this website.

## Viewer Privacy

IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC., Inc. does not collect personal information such as names, e-mail addresses, postal addresses, or telephone numbers. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

## IP Addresses

As noted above, we do not collect any personal information on this Web site. We do, however, collect and store information about your Internet connection when you visit our Web site to read or download information, such as reports, news, etc. We use this information to track Web site use, measure site traffic, and improve site navigation and information. We collect information that identifies: · The name of the domain you access the Internet with. · The type of web browsing software you use to view our site. · The date and time of your access. · The platform you are using (i.e. Windows, Macintosh or Unix). This information is never sold, given or disclosed to third parties. This information is used internally to administer our web site, provide better services to the public, and provide aggregate traffic statistics to IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC. staff. No personal information is collected

## Hyperlinks

Additionally, this site contains links to other sites. IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC., Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites unless operated directly by IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC., Inc. We encourage you to note when you leave our website and read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information.

## Acceptance and Jurisdiction

By using this site, you agree that you have read, understand and will abide, and be bound, by the terms of this Web Site Privacy and Policies ("Terms"). If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not use the IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC. web site. These Terms shall be governed in all respects in accordance with the laws of the State of Iowa without regard to the conflict or choice of law rules thereof. Courts sitting in the State of Iowa, federal and state, shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising hereunder. IOWA NETWORK SERVICES, INC. reserves the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact [webmaster@iowanetworkservices.com](mailto:webmaster@iowanetworkservices.com).

Iowa Network Services, Inc.  
Information Systems  
4201 Corporate Drive  
West Des Moines, IA 50266-5906  
PHONE: (515) 830-0110  
FAX: (515) 830-0123
